A message the Lord said I should give to my African Continent:
No African country can succeed alone
Africans need each other to develop
tell your neighbour
West Africa needs Southern Africa to develop
Southern Africa needs West Africa to develop
North Africa needs East Africa to develop
and East Africa needs North Africa to develop
No one is self-sufficient
We can not do without each other
Everyone has a contribution
Whether you are poor, rich or an immigrant
everyone has a contribution
for the development of Africa
at the level we are now.
Dear Africans,
we should not let
other fellow Africans feel unwelcome to our countries
With regard to the issue
of illegal immigrants,
drugs and other crimes
our duty is to inform law enforcement agencies.
That is our duty - to give them useful information about issues like that
In our respective countries, our duty is to inform law enforcement agencies.
It is only when they fail to carry out their duty,
that we citizens can lawfully protest.
I want to show you
a little video before I continue talking
There is no country in Africa that is not involved in what you are about to watch.
What is the cause?
Because Africa has neglected her youth
Africa has neglected her youth
the youth- they have neglected them
Africa has abandon the youth to themselves
Whereas tomorrow Africa is the youth.
But we have neglected them, that is the cause of this frustrations.
When I think about the future of Africa- I have sleepless nights.
Please can you play this cassette for me - please lets watch.
In the mediterranean of the cost of libya, this unstable fish boat is overloaded
with migrants and refugees.
So there is a horrible inevitability in what is about to happen.
The boat is starting to tilt
then the situation becomes so much worse.
Many jump to the water of the mediterranean before the boat completely capsizes.
Moments later it is completely overturned
Scores swam away from the shipwreck
but five people were found dead in the water.
But this man with 561 others were rescued
They are now safe but the scene of utter desperation we witness this time last year.
It constantly repeated itself.
They are your children, they are the youth of Africa
All- they are youth of Africa
There is no country in Africa that is not represented there.
This are your children that claim they have travelled outside the country.
Many of them are there - looking for green pastures.
Africa has neglected her youth.
Africa has abandoned the youth - to themselves.
Africa has failed to provide green pastures.
When I think about the future of Africa,
I have sleepless nights.
Within Africa, If we are now fighting within ourselves.
Look at what is happening in other continent concerning Africa.
Withi continents there is fight among the youth
Everything looks gloomy,
frustrating,
hopeless,
dark and darksome dull and sunless.
Africa- Unite!
No African country can succeed alone,
we need each other to develop.
So, If we cannot understand ourselves within Africa
How can they understand us in other continents?
I was so troubled, and the Lord gave me the word.
I want to volunteer myself, and I know God has touched many Africans.
I know as am talking God has touched many Africans.
Many Africans that are in a position to help and I know many of them are crying.
I am at your service.
We will not only sit in the church alone
You will learn that I will travel to the meetings with people
that are ready to talk about the challenges ahead.
Yes- look at the ministry
All counties, races are inside the church
God says he has realised you
He says he has touched many people that are in the position of honor and authority.
They are ready, lets come together- lets talk about the youth
that have been neglected.
They have been neglected
They have been abandoned to themselves.
No provision for our youths
When you are counting the best universities in the world
hardly will you see a single university from Africa among 1-500.
There is no single African university.
can you see the decayness
The technology is zero.
You are flying to Dubai, you are flying to Turkey, you are flying to New york,
when are they flying into your country?
Look at your age, are you not going to witness that transformation
when Africa will become the centre where people will begin to discover themselves.
You are getting old.
Now your children, where is that future for them?
they gave been abandoned.
Because they have been abandoned that is the cause of frustrations.
Frustration can make anyone to do anything.
When you realise you are a graduate and there is no job and
you are looking at your age wonder where are you going.
And everyday things are becoming worse
It is frustration
Dear Africa, we should not let other fellow African to feel unwelcome in our counties.
tell your neighbour, fellow Africa.
we should not let other fellow Africa feel unwelcome in our countries
Again!
No African country can succeed, can develope alone.
When it now comes to the issue of people taking drugs to a country or crime.
Our duty is to work with law enforcement
by giving them useful information about this people that are doing this.
That is our duty.
But if they now fail to do anything - then, lawfully we can protest.
Other nations are now laying bans on immigrants
definitely we Africans we should awake and rescue our people.
If there is ban in the immigrants, definitely this is the time we should awake.
What can we do to rescue our people?
Because this immigrants we are talking about 90% are Africans.
So they are coming back home.
And we have many of them are home already
on employment?
And we have millions coming to join on employment at home.
Where is the peace?
No matter how much you are blessed you can never have peace
if people around you are suffering.